<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>642.studio</title><link>https://642.studio/</link><description>Recent content on 642.studio</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 09:51:00 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://642.studio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>MedMen</title><link>https://642.studio/portfolio/medmen/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://642.studio/portfolio/medmen/</guid><description>
&lt;p>
Staff augmentation, assisting with mobile, web, and backend applications.
&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Toucan iOS</title><link>https://642.studio/portfolio/toucan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://642.studio/portfolio/toucan/</guid><description>
&lt;p>
The Toucan iOS Client and CI/CD delivery for Apple Platforms. Done in collaboration with &lt;a
href="mailto:hello@themobile.team">The Mobile Team&lt;/a>.
&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Resonate Recorder</title><link>https://642.studio/portfolio/resonate-recorder/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://642.studio/portfolio/resonate-recorder/</guid><description>
&lt;p>
The mobile recorder companion app to &lt;a href="https://resonaterecordings.com">Resonate Recordings&lt;/a>' podcast
production services.
&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Resume</title><link>https://642.studio/resume/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 11:24:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://642.studio/resume/</guid><description>642.studio LLC Owner and Operator Santa Monica, CA February 2022 - Current Software solutions consultant excelling at mobile and backend web services Ten years of experience working across many industries and disciplines with teams all over the globe Experienced with Swift Application Development Typescript/Javascript Front and Backend Applications Task Automation Envoy Senior iOS engineer (Remote) San Francisco, CA January 2018 - February 2022 Developed features for Desks product during period where annual recurring revenue grew from one to ten million dollars Collaborated with product team to develop technical specifications and story break downs for execution during sprints Delivered functionality across the stack Ruby and Kotlin backends as well as the iOS client MedMen Staff Software Engineer Culver City, CA July 2018 - June 2020 Delivered rewards platform to improve customer retention and incentives return visits Delivered delivery platform to expand customer base and create additional revenue Delivered applications for merchandising products in store Maintained in house point of sale application and related GraphQL APIs interviewologist Consulting Software Engineer Los Angeles, CA May 2018 - July 2018 Pray LLC.</description></item><item><title>Better Looking Boy</title><link>https://642.studio/portfolio/better-look/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://642.studio/portfolio/better-look/</guid><description>
&lt;p>
BetterLook was a companion application for &lt;a href="http://thelavenderscaremusic.com">The Lavender Scare&lt;/a>'s
single 'Better Looking Boy'.
&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Pinnd</title><link>https://642.studio/portfolio/pinnd/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://642.studio/portfolio/pinnd/</guid><description>
&lt;p>
Pinnd was a third party client for the website &lt;a href="https://pinboard.in/">Pinboard&lt;/a>.
&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>